{
    "what_hero": {
        "question1": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Ana Amari?",
            "answer": "ana"
        },
        "question2": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Elizabeth Caledonia “Calamity” Ashe?",
            "answer": "ashe"
        },
        "question3": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Jean-Baptiste Augustin?",
            "answer": "baptiste"
        },
        "question4": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: SST Laboratories Siege Automaton E54?",
            "answer": "bastion"
        },
        "question5": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Brigitte Lindholm?",
            "answer": "brigitte"
        },
        "question6": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Hana Song?",
            "answer": "d.va"
        },
        "question7": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Akande Ogundimu?",
            "answer": "doomfist"
        },
        "question8": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Genji Shimada?",
            "answer": "genji"
        },
        "question9": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Hanzo Shimada?",
            "answer": "hanzo"
        },
        "question10": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Jamison Fawkes?",
            "answer": "junkrat"
        },
        "question11": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Lúcio Correia dos Santos?",
            "answer": "lúcio"
        },
        "question12": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Jesse McCree?",
            "answer": "mccree"
        },
        "question13": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Mei-Ling Zhou?",
            "answer": "mei"
        },
        "question14": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Angela Ziegler?",
            "answer": "mercy"
        },
        "question15": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Moira O’Deorain?",
            "answer": "moira"
        },
        "question16": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Orisa?",
            "answer": "orisa"
        },
        "question17": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Fareeha Amari?",
            "answer": "pharah"
        },
        "question18": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Gabriel Reyes?",
            "answer": "reaper"
        },
        "question19": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Reinhardt Wilhelm?",
            "answer": "reinhardt"
        },
        "question20": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Mako Rutledge?",
            "answer": "roadhog"
        },
        "question21": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Siebren de Kuiper?",
            "answer": "sigma"
        },
        "question22": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: John Francis 'Jack' Morrison?",
            "answer": "soldier: 76"
        },
        "question23": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Olivia Colomar?",
            "answer": "sombra"
        },
        "question24": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Satya Vaswani?",
            "answer": "symmetra"
        },
        "question25": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Torbjörn Lindholm?",
            "answer": "torbjörn"
        },
        "question26": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Lena Oxton?",
            "answer": "tracer"
        },
        "question27": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Amélie Lacroix (née Guillard)?",
            "answer": "widowmaker"
        },
        "question28": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Winston?",
            "answer": "winston"
        },
        "question29": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Hammond?",
            "answer": "wrecking ball"
        },
        "question30": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Aleksandra Zaryanova?",
            "answer": "zarya"
        },
        "question31": {
            "question": "What hero has the real name: Tekhartha Zenyatta?",
            "answer": "zenyatta"
        }
    } 
}
